Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Business Records, 1962-1964; Series VI; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Sales book, 1962 September-1963 May (Box 184)
  - Sales tax forms, 1963-1964 (Box 184)
  - Receipts, 1963 January-1964 December; 24 folders (Box 184)
- Oversize Material, 1851-2002; Series VII; 1.6 linear feet (15 boxes)
  Organized into eight subseries: Prints that Depict the American West, Collected Newspaper Material, Exhibition Posters, Book Jacket Galleys, Bird's-Eye Views and Maps, Humboldt County Material, Research on Photographers, and Other Material.
  Oversize material larger than 18 inches in size and smaller than 24 inches related to projects and interests of Palmquist.
  - Prints that Depict the American West
    Engravings and lithographs collected by Palmquist that document sites and events in the American West.
    - California
      - "Birdseye View of General Sutter's Old Ranch," Thompson & West, 1879 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Felling the Red-Wood-Trees of California -- Drawn by Charles Graham," Harper's Weekly, 1886 October 30 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - Luther L. Holden, "Through Picturesque America," Ladies Home Journal, Parts 5, 7, and 9, circa 1900 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Mirror Lake, Yosemite Valley," D. Appleton and Company, 1872 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Monterey and the Hotel Del Monte -- Drawn by Charles Graham," Harper's Weekly, 1887 April 16 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Mount Shasta," D. Appleton and Company, 1873 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Native Californians Lassoing a Bear," D. Appleton and Company, 1873 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Photographs from California," The Illustrated London News, 1853 January 29 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Sacramento City, California," Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851 August 23 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "San Jose, Santa Clara County, California," reprinted by Leo K. Brown, 1974 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "A Series of Interesting Sketches and Scenes in California," Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1852 October 30 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Sketches in the American Far West," The Illustrated London News, 1880 April 17 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Souvenir," a folded souvenir with lithograph depictions of photographs of sites in California by Lawrence & Houseworth, circa 1870 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "A View of San Francisco, California," Ballou's Pictorial, 1857 July 25 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "View of the Custom House at San Francisco, California," Rebel Beauty, circa 1864 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "View of the Grand Plaza or Public Square, San Francisco, California," Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1852 March 27 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "View of the Town of Marysville, California," Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1872 March 13 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - Photocopies of California from the Pictorial Union, 1854 July 4; 2 folders (Box 185 (Oversize))
    - Modoc War
      Engravings in Harper's Weekly based on photographs by Louis H. Heller and Eadweard J. Muybridge that document the Modoc War, or Modoc Campaign (also known as the Lava Beds War), an armed conflict between the Native American Modoc tribe and the United States Army in southern Oregon and northern California from 1872 to 1873.
      - "The Modocs -- Murder of General Canby and the Rev. Dr. Thomas," Harper's Weekly, 1873 May 3 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Modocs Scalping and Torturing Prisoners" and "The Modoc War -- Soldiers Recovering the Bodies of the Slain," Harper's Weekly, 1873 May 17 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "Modoc Brave Lying in Wait for a Shot," "On the Look-out for an Attack on a Picket Station," "Modoc Squaws," "Captain Jack's Late Stronghold," and "Warm Spring Indians Scouting," Harper's Weekly, 1873 June 21 (Box 185 (Oversize))
      - "The Modoc War -- Captain Jack's Cave in the Lava Beds" and "The Modocs -- Murder of General Canby," Harper's Weekly, 1873 June 28 (Box 185 (Oversize))
  - Collected Newspaper Material
    This subseries consists of specimen newspapers, commemorative issues, tear sheets, and scrapbooks with clippings related to sites and events chiefly in Humboldt County, California, as well as other localities in California and Nevada, including published examples of Palmquist's photography.
    Many of the newspapers during the winter of 1964 and 1965, as well as all the tear sheets, document the Christmas flood of 1964, a major flood that took place in the Pacific Northwest and California between December 18, 1964 and January 7, 1965. Palmquist created many of the newspaper photographs attributed to the Associated Press and United Press Syndicate.
    Organized under five headings: Complete Newspapers, Newspaper Tear Sheets from the Christmas Flood of 1964, Newspaper Tear Sheets with Articles by Andrew Martin Genzoli, Scrapbooks with Newspaper Clippings Related to Palmquist, and Newspaper Material Related to Humboldt County or Photography.
    - Complete Newspapers
      - The Klamath News (Orleans Bar, California), 1865 August 17 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Lariat (Virginia City, Nevada), 1877 August (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Daily Evening Signal (Eureka, California), 1877 November 3 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - West Coast Signal (Eureka, California), 1877 November 28 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Daily Times-Telephone (Eureka, California), 1883 April 27 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Daily Times-Telephone (Eureka, California), 1884 April 3 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Advance (Springville, California), 1888 September 13 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Home Journal (Hydesville, California), 1890 January 25 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Footlight (Eureka, California), 1890 October 11, 13, and 14 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Nerve (Eureka, California), 1893 January 7 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Weekly Report (Ferndale, California), 1893 January 11 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Nerve (Eureka, California), 1893 March 4 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Our Paper (Alton, California), 1893 March 4 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Daily Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1894 December 1 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Daily Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1895 December 24 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Eel River Valley Advance (Fortuna, California), 1896 May 30 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Arcata Union, 1897 January 1 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Daily Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1897 January 10 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Semi-Weekly Ferndale Exchange, 1899 October 9 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Wave (Seattle, Washington), photocopy, 1899 October 14 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1900 June 9 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - Methodist Church Bulletin (Eureka, California), 1905 February 10 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Humboldt Beacon (Fortuna, California), 1913 January 17 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Dinsmore Record (Grizzly Bluff, California), photocopy, circa 1914 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Redwood Bark (Eureka, California), 1926 September 17 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Scandalous Screamer (Eureka, California), 1928 May 29 (Box 186 (Oversize))
      - The Ferndale Enterprise, 1952 August 22; 3 folders (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - The Eureka Independent, 1953 February 4 (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1954 February 8 (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1954 February; 16 folders (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - Blue Lake Advocate, 1954 May 27; 2 folders (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1961 January 12 (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1961 January 16 (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - The A. Brizard Century, special issue of Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1963 May (Box 187 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1964 December 22 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 22 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1964 December 23 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 23 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1964 December 24 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 24 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1964 December 25 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 25 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1964 December 26 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 26 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 27 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1964 December 28 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1964 December 31 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - Eureka Newspapers, Inc., The Thousand Year Flood!, 1965 February 15-16 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - The Redwood Record (Garberville, California), circa 1965 (Box 188 (Oversize))
      - North Coast Outdoors (Eureka, California), 1968 January 12 (Box 189 (Oversize))
      - The Union (Arcata, California), 1976 July 29 (Box 189 (Oversize))
      - The Valley Oracle (Ferndale, California), 1976 (Box 189 (Oversize))
      - Eel River Valley Advance (Fortuna Depot Museum, Fortuna, California), circa 1976 (Box 189 (Oversize))
        Reprint of the May 30, 1896 issue
      - The Times-Standard (Eureka, California) - "The North Coast Scene", 1977 December 15 (Box 189 (Oversize))
      - California Living Magazine, a supplement for the San Francisco Sunday Examiner and Chronicle, 1978 November 12 (Box 189 (Oversize))
      - The Times-Standard (Eureka, California), 1979 March 25; 3 folders (Box 189 (Oversize))
      - Anne's Humboldt Scrapbook (Eureka, California), 1985 (Box 189 (Oversize))
    - Newspaper Tear Sheets from the Christmas Flood of 1964, 1964 December-1965; 51 folders (Box 190 (Oversize))
    - Newspaper Tear Sheets with Articles by Andrew Martin Genzoli, 1951 January-July; 10 folders (Box 191 (Oversize))
      Tear sheets from the The Humboldt Times newspaper with articles on historical and cultural topics in Humboldt County by Andrew Martin Genzoli
    - Scrapbooks with Newspaper Clippings Related to Palmquist
      Clippings related to photography by Palmquist from Humboldt County newspapers mounted in spiral-bound Strathmore Watercolor Cold Press Paper Pads, 18 by 24 inches.
      - Scrapbook, 1961-1962 (Box 192 (Oversize))
        - Clippings removed from the scrapbook, 1961-1962 (Box 192 (Oversize))
      - Scrapbook, 1962-1964 (Box 193 (Oversize))
        - Clippings removed from the scrapbook, 1962-1964 (Box 193 (Oversize))
    - Newspaper Material Related to Humboldt County or Photography
      - Clipping with an advertisement for A. Crocker & Brothers in the Daily Standard (Eureka, California), 1894 December 10 (Box 194 (Oversize))
      - Supplements, "Mechanical and Agricultural Fair," Daily Humboldt Standard (Eureka, California), 1896 August 22, 1899 August 16; 2 folders (Box 194 (Oversize))
      - "Humboldt County, California, School Districts, Teachers and Trustees, July, 1901," Daily Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1901 August 18 (Box 194 (Oversize))
      - Advertisements for the town of Fieldbrook in Daily Humboldt Times (Eureka, California), 1901 December 15-29, 1902 December 8; 3 folders (Box 194 (Oversize))
      - "Photographic Salon at Exposition Park" and "A Series of Interesting Flashes Caught by a Wandering Cameraman," Los Angeles Sunday Times, 1921 December 25 (Box 194 (Oversize))
      - "Whale Processing 'Big Job'; Plant Busy Scene," Humboldt Standard, 1951 March 29 (Box 194 (Oversize))
      - Evans, Jeff, "Past Perfect, Daguerreotypes Capture History in the Making," The Bulletin, (Norwich, Connecticut), 1989 November 26 (Box 194 (Oversize))
        Article about daguerreotype collector Matthew R. Isenburg
  - Exhibition Posters
    This subseries consists of posters for exhibitions organized by Palmquist or including material from his collection, as well as posters for exhibitions he collected related to chiefly photography.
    - Toad Hill, Other Nonsense and Jennifer, Humboldt State University, mock up, 1973-1974 Winter (Box 195 (Broadside))
    - Toad Hill, Other Nonsense and Jennifer, Humboldt State University, 1974? February 9-16 (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Camera Captured Characters and Curiosities, c. 1870-1900, Humboldt State University, 1974 January (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Andreas Feininger: A Retrospective, International Center of Photography, 1976 September-November (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Josef Sudek (1896-1976): A Retrospective, International Center of Photography, 1977 May-July (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Weegee the Famous: A Retrospective Exhibition, International Center of Photography, 1977 September-November (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Photographers of the Humboldt Bay Region, 1850-1950, California State University, 1978 September-November (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Figure Drawing: Robert Craner, Humboldt State University, 1979 November-December (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Timothy O'Sullivan, Fraenkel Gallery, 1980 January-February (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Remembrances of the Near East: Photographs by Bonfils, 1867-1907, International Center of Photography, 1980 May-September (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Color as Form: A History of Color Photography, traveling exhibition, 1982 April-June (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - The Era of the French Calotype, International Center of Photography, 1982 September-November (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Carleton E. Watkins: Photographer of the American West, Amon Carter Museum, galley, circa 1982-1983 (Box 197 (Broadside))
    - Carleton E. Watkins: Photographer of the American West, Amon Carter Museum, 1983 April 1- May 22 (Box 198 (Broadside))
    - Particulars: Selections from the Miller-Plummer Collection of Photography, traveling exhibition, 1983 June-1984 March (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Louise Halsey: An American Pictorialist, Humboldt State University, mock-up for the exhibition poster, 1985 January (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Louise Halsey: An American Pictorialist, Humboldt State University, 1985 January (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Photographs from the Wm. B. Becker Collection, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1987 August-October (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Tom Knight: Of Light and Life, a Retrospective, Humboldt State University, 1988 February-March (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - More Than Meets the Eye, National Archives of Canada, 1989 (Box 199 (Broadside))
    - Women in Photography International, Royal Photographic Society, 1990 October 27-1991 January 6 (Box 200 (Broadside))
    - The Secret Pleasures of Daguerreotypes from the William B. Becker Collection, Southeast Museum of Photography, 1993 January 5-March 26 (Box 201 (Broadside))
    - Edwardian Women Photographers: Eveleen Myers, Alice Hughes, Christina Broom, and Olive Edis, National Portrait Gallery, 1994 July-September (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Dody, Weston, Thompson: A Selection of Black & White and Color Photographs from the Last Fifty Years, California State University Chico, 1998 January-February (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Ira Latour: A Retrospective Exhibition of Photography and Cinematography, California State University Chico, 1998 February -March (Box 196 (Oversize))
    - Ericson Photograph Collection, Humboldt State University, 2001 October 2-29 (Box 202 (Broadside))
    - Shadow Catchers, Dell'Arte International School of Physical Theatre, undated (Box 203 (Broadside))
    - Posters for exhibitions by photographers, including Robert A Sobieszek, Imogen Cunningham, and Eugène Atget, undated (Box 204 (Broadside))
    - Ellen Land-Weber, Company Town Scotia, undated (Box 205 (Broadside))
    - Posters for exhibitions, undated (Box 206 (Broadside))
  - Book Jacket and Illustration Galleys
    Galleys for dust jackets and illustrations for books authored, edited, or co-authored by Palmquist.
    - Galley of a dust jacket for Alan Clark Miller, Photographer of a Frontier: The Photographs of Peter Britt (Eureka, California: Interface California Corporation), 1976 (Box 207 (Broadside))
    - Galley of a dust jacket for Wallace E. Martin, Sail & Steam on the Northern California Coast, 1850-1900 (San Francisco: Published by the National Maritime Museum Association), 1983 (Box 208 (Broadside))
    - Galley of a dust jacket for Peter E. Palmquist and Lincoln Kilian, The Photographers of the Humboldt Bay Region, Volume 7, A. W. Ericson. (Arcata, California: Peter E. Palmquist), 1989 (Box 209 (Oversize))
    - Galley of a dust jacket for Peter E. Palmquist, The Daguerreian Annual 1990: Official Yearbook of The Daguerreian Society (Eureka, California: Daguerreian Society) (Box 209 (Oversize))
    - Galley of a dust jacket for Peter E. Palmquist and Thomas R. Kailbourn, Pioneer Photographers of the Far West: A Biographical Dictionary, 1840-1865 (Stanford, California: Stanford University Press), 2002 (Box 209 (Oversize))
    - Galleys for illustration in Peter E. Palmquist, With Nature's Children: Emma B. Freeman, 1880-1928 - Camera and Brus h (Eureka, Calif: Interface California Corporation, circa 1976 (Box 210 (Broadside))
    - Material on Women in Photography, including galleys and dust jackets, undated (Box 211 (Broadside))
  - Bird's-Eye Views and Maps
    - Bird's-eye view of Marysville and Yuba City, California, undated (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Bird's-eye view of Sutter City, California, undated (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Doolittle, A. J., and Grafton Tyler Brown, The Official Township Map of Humboldt Co., Cal.: Carefully Compiled from U.S. Land and Coast Surveys, with Personal Observations (San Francisco, California: A.J. Doolittle), 1865 (Box 213 (Broadside))
    - Hoffmann, Charles Frederick, and J. T. Gardner, Map of Portion of the Sierra Nevada Adjacent to the Yosemite Valley (Sacramento: Geological Survey of California, 1867), photographs (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Map of camera locations for images in Robert H. Vance, Catalogue of Daguerreotype Panoramic Views in California (New York: Baker, Godwin & Company, 1851), photographic print (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Maps of Fort Gaston, California, 1879, photocopies (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Map of Fort Humboldt, California, 1861, Photostat negative (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Map of Humboldt County, California (Box 212 (Oversize))
    - Map that shows the pre-contact distribution of American tribes in northwestern California, undated (Box 214 (Broadside))
    - United States Coast Survey, Reconnaissance of Trinidad Bay, California (Washington, D.C.: United States Coast Survey), 1851 (Box 212 (Oversize))
  - Humboldt County Material
    - Advertisements from a newspaper in Eureka, California, for Warren & Welden and Darden & Hodgson, 1894 December (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Campaign poster for Steve Harvey for Judge with an illustration by Stock Schlueter, 1984 (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Circular for Fannie M. Francis, a cosmetician in Eureka, California, circa 1920 (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - The Democratic Standard (Eureka, California), 1883 June 9 (Box 216 (Broadside))
    - Drawings by Joseph Goldsborough Bruff of sites in Humboldt County in 1851 and held by the Huntington Library, photocopies (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Drawing of a paper boy peddling Humboldt County newspapers, including the Humboldt Times Standard (Eureka, California) and Little Valley Gleaner (Rohnerville, California), circa 1881, halftone copy photograph (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Drawings of buildings in Arcata, California, in 1851, photocopies (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Panoramic photograph of the Dolber and Carson Lumber Company in Eureka, California, by Dold and Dold, copy photograph (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Poster commemorating the thirtieth anniversary of the KHSU public radio station signed by the artist, Jim McKicker, 1990 (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Program for plays at the Ingomar Theater in Eureka, California, 1906 December 25-27 (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Program for the play, "Old Maid's Convention," at the Odd Fellows Hall, Blue Lake, California, circa 1915 (Box 215 (Oversize))
    - Richard B. Davis Company, Aerial photograph of Arcata, California, 1985 February 28 (Box 215 (Oversize))
  - Research on Photographers
    - Table of photographers in San Francisco, California, in the United States Census of 1910, undated (Box 217 (Broadside))
    - Tables of photographers in Humboldt County, California, undated (Box 218 (Broadside))
  - Other Material
    - Advertisements for photographers in L'Echo du Pacifique (San-Francisco, California) newspaper, copy photographs, 1854 February 22 (Box 219 (Oversize))
    - Cartoon La Daguerreotypomanie, 1840, by Théodore Maurisset, reprint (Box 219 (Oversize))
    - Material related to the layout of Toyon, a literary magazine sponsored by the Department of English at Humboldt State University and designed by Peter Palmquist, 1971 (Box 219 (Oversize))
    - Panoramic photograph of San Francisco, California, 1855, taken by George Robinson Fardon, copy photograph (Box 219 (Oversize))
    - Poster for the 4th Congreso de Historia de la Fotografía (1839-1939) in Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1995 October 21 (Box 219 (Oversize))
    - Poster for an extension course, A History of Photography in Humboldt County, c. 1840-1940, taught by Peter Palmquist at Humboldt State University, 1974 January (Box 219 (Oversize))
    - Poster of View-Master Reels, undated (Box 220 (Broadside))
- Audiovisual Material, 1964-2003; Series VIII; 3.9 linear feet (8 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Series III is organized into four subseries: Reel-to-reel tapes, Audiocassettes, Motion Picture Films, and Videotapes.
  Audiovisual material collected by or featuring Palmquist.
  - Reel-to-reel tapes
    - Side 2: Steichen and his Camera, circa 1964-1969 (Box 221)
    - Weapons of Gordon Parks, circa 1967 (Box 221)
    - John Del Pozzo, attributed, Soundtrack for Auracaria, circa 1965-1970 (Box 221)
      See also: Auracaria, Boxes 338-339
    - Peter Bunnell, Museum of Modern Art, "The Photograph - The Thing Itself", 1969 December (Box 221)
    - Garry Winogrand, California Institute of the Arts, 1974 February (Box 221)
    - Ralph Gibson, "Nothing is Known," Pasadena Art Museum, 1974 March (Box 221)
    - Michael Andrews, The Mind's Eye: Dialogues in Photography, lecture series at the University of California, Los Angeles, 1974 May (Box 221)
    - Jack Welpott and Judy Dater, The Contemporary Woman, 1974 May (Box 221)
    - Side 2: Robert M. Doty, Photo-Secession, 1880-1910, University of California, Los Angeles, 1975 April-May (Box 221)
    - Beaumont Newhall, "Photo Eye of the 20's", Pomona Claremont College, 1975 May (Box 221)
    - John Upton, Concentration Exercise, History of Photography, 1975 July (Box 221)
    - Side 2: Robert Sobieszek, Photography in the Middle East 1839-1870, Photo Album Gallery, 1976 May-June (Box 221)
    - Peter Palmquist at the International Center of Photography, 1977 March (Box 221)
    - Wright Morris, Pomona College Seminar, 1978 April (Box 221)
    - Edmund Teske Lecture, undated (Box 221)
      Possibly a lecture in the The Mind's Eye: Dialogues in Photography lecture series at the University of California, Los Angeles, May 20, 1974
    - Future of Photography, undated (Box 221)
    - Leland Rice, "The Nude in Photography", undated (Box 221)
  - Audiocassettes
    - Erickson Tapes of Mrs. Christensen, 1973 February (Box 222)
    - The Swanland Tapes, 1973 February 24 (Box 222)